myyogaonline.com 2006-06-23

# Privacy Policy

---  
   
|   
---  
  
Subscribe to our **FREE** newsletter  
full of inspirational articles on yoga, recipes, body care and more  
to help you maintain your path  
to health and wellness.

Receive a  
 **FREE YOGA VIDEO**  
when you sign up

|   
---  

|   |   |    
---|---|---  
**Yoga and The Spine**  
  
Strong muscles support your frame and give good posture. Yoga keeps the muscles strong and is a caretaker of the spine, structural core of the body. Lengthening and strengthening it, yoga keeps the spine limber and agile like it was when we were small children. Since the spine houses the central nervous system (which also includes the brain), keeping the spine healthy will enhance all other functions of the human body. This means the body will move with grace and ease, feel and look better, and age well.  

|  |  |  |  |  |  |  | ****  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |    
---|---|---  
  | By using this site, you indicate your agreement of My Yoga Online?s Privacy Policy.  
My Yoga Online does not sell, loan, trade, or give personal information collected on this website. All information, including email addresses, is used solely for our internal marketing and is not sold or exchanged to any third party. My Yoga Online does not support ?spam marketers?. We ensure that your personal information is private and will never be shared with other organizations. At times, we may disclose member information only in the form of aggregate statistical data that doesn't identify individual members. This statistical information helps our partners and sponsors to understand the collective characteristics of our members and to target their messages effectively. This disclosed information will not provide partners and sponsors with any personal information including name, address, email address, and especially credit card information.

 **Secure Server Statement**   
Secure Ordering ? My Yoga Online ensures that the personal information you transmit to us through this website remains protected. My Yoga Online keeps your online order information safe by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Your order is encrypted by SSL to prevent the decoding of personal information and credit card information by anyone other than My Yoga Online.

Members will be advised regarding any changes to this policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement please 

[Contact Us](http://www.myyogaonline.com/contactus.html).  
|   
|   
---
